<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on samh</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on samh</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 11:55:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>There Really Is a Difference</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/books/there-really-is-a-difference-showers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 11:55:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/books/there-really-is-a-difference-showers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There Really Is a Difference by Renald E. Showers&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve entered into quite a few discussions on Dispensationalism. The people I discussed it with held their position on it (for or against) quite strongly yet most did not actually understand what Dispensationalism actually contains. The explanations I got on Dispensationalism were always either confusing or incomplete. I heard that Dispensationalists don&amp;rsquo;t believe in the Old Testament. I have heard that Dispensationalism is seeing a distinction between Israel and the Church. I have heard that Dispensationalism reads the Bible more literally. I have heard that Dispensationalism is about the different ways God relates to people throughout history. I was unsatisfied with these descriptions. I dug into Dispensationalism some more using resources from Reformed perspectives and the more I understood it the more I did not trust it. A comment on a particular YouTube video on Dispensationalism struck me, &amp;ldquo;I was a Dispensational until I tried to explain Dispensationalism.&amp;rdquo; And that basically summed up my thoughts on the idea. That it is a confusing system of understanding the Bible. That it sees the Bible in a disjointed way. That it reads things woodenly and misses proper understandings of passages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthodoxy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/books/orthodoxy-chesterton/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 11:00:22 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/books/orthodoxy-chesterton/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Orthodoxy by G.K. Chesterton&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
